Over here!
Get her! Don't let her go!
MUNDANE
No security cameras.
They didn't put them up in the alley.
Let's get out of here!
Jo Anna?
Your kind always thinks
that having superpowers
means you can do whatever you want.
Do you contribute
anything at all to society?
Do you even pay taxes?
Where's your little friends, huh?
Why do you keep making me do
the same thing again?
I think I'll just roast you, Anna.
Didn't see the weather forecast, huh?
Aw, poor thing.
It's raining.
Your little superpower's cute,
but you know what's even better
in this day and age?
Real power.
She's right.
These superpowers aren't any greater
than power itself.
It's actually more like…
How should I put this?
Hmm.
It's more like the difference
between a jalapeño and a habanero.
Or perhaps between a housefly
and a hornet.
So what I'm trying to say is,
I'm toast.
MISSING PERSON
LEE HWA-JIN, AGE 23
LAST SEEN AT JONGNO NAKSIN STATION
We haven't heard from Hwa-jin in a week.
Yeah.
Bun-mi, I think it's best
if you learn to control that rage
you're holding onto inside.
Yeah, I'm working on that.
I thought you were on a diet.
I'm having one meal a day
where I can eat whatever I want.
Didn't you have dinner with me earlier?
Well, this is dessert.
Anyway, you drink, like, every day, so…
Look at this. Have you seen this?
Crazy. Hey, everyone!
-Mm, that guy didn't even try hiding it.
-There's a man pulling the bus back up.
He's a total Superman.
No, no! He's like Spider-Man!
-Hey.
-Right, it was zoomed in.
Oh, wow!
He's pulling it back on the bridge!
The cops took him in after that.
We are watching a hero being born…
All those shiny things falling off of him.
That looks like money.
Yeah.
This is completely real,
what you are seeing right now, folks!
Is that a power our kind has always had?
Back in the day.
All right, let's go get him.
Drive.
-You drive.
-Huh?
No, I can't.
I need to finish my shift. I can't. Later.
There's a lot of people
who are gonna want him.
We need to find him first.
Oh, come on.
Hey. Wait. Just wait a minute.
We could get caught doing that.
Uh, if they're after him,
then they might come after us,
and Hwa-jin's still missing.
Uh-uh. What are we gonna do,
just you and me?
Bun-mi!
He's different, this guy.
He could bring an end to this war of ours.
I'm royally fucked.
I didn't do anything wrong,
but I'm locked up
in a holding cell anyway.
I heard he's that bus guy.
That's him. The crazy one.
I don't buy it.
Hey there.
I heard you pushed the bus over, man.
Are you serious?
No, that wasn't me.
I didn't do that.
This bastard. This guy's out of his mind.
-You wanna push me too?
-Uh, no, I don't.
I'd rather not…
-Look at that.
-Not much to you, is there?
I knew it wasn't him.
He's nothing!
Keep it down in there!
Calm down, all right?
Sorry, sir. I didn't start it.
I wanna go home.
I wish I could just take a shower,
scroll on my phone, and go to bed.
Just to be able to go to work tomorrow.
I can't believe
I'm wishing I could go to work.
Dear God.
Please help me.
If you get in trouble, call this number.
What's that idiot doing now?
What's gotten into him?
I can't believe him.
CHAIRWOMAN PARK JEONG-JA
JEONGJA LOANS
-Hello?
-Oh.
Yeah. Hello, this is, uh, Kang Sang-ung.
My father said I should call this number
if I found myself, uh, in a tough spot.
And what would your father's name be?
He's Kang Dong-gi.
That's my dad.
Last name Kang, Dong-ja, Dong-gi.
GA TO KIM
KANG DONG-GI
LOAN AGREEMENT
All right, then.
How's your father? Is he doing well?
HOLDING CELL
Thank you.
Guess that worked.
MY MIN-SUK (50)
I'm dead meat.
Excuse me, uh, the hero
from the bus crash is here, isn't he?
Detective! Detective!
We will provide a statement
during the briefing.
Mr. Kang. Mr. Kang Sang-ung?
Oh.
I can't imagine how stressful it's been.
Yeah, but
who are you?
JEONGJA LOANS
Chairwoman Park, Mr. Kang's been released.
Chairwoman?
Hello.
You don't have any money, do you?
What?
Get in.
Let me give you a lift to your house.
I get the feeling
I shouldn't have made that call.
I saw the news.
It's incredibly admirable what you did.
Even I was proud of you.
Aside from that,
how'd you think to call
with all that chaos surrounding you?
Well, first, uh,
thank you for helping me.
Good manners too.
Be honest,
you can't wait to find out
how I know who your father is.
Right?
I don't care. Not at all.
Dong-gi oppa has extensive debt with me,
as it turns out.
I'm in a car
with a woman I've never met before.
She's calling my dad "oppa"
and telling me he owes her money.
This is weird.
Including interest
at the maximum rate that's allowed,
the grand total is three billion won.
Let me out.
BEOMHA RANCH
MAN LIFTS FALLING BUS,
PREVENTING CASUALTIES
I'm sure Dad's gonna like that.
Hello.
I bet you feel brand-new
being ordinary again.
It's like you're reincarnated.
You should thank me, actually.
Is she dead?
No.
Damn it. This one's no fun.
Everyone's always making such a fuss.
It's pretty.
And if I injected this?
What?
Take it.
We're still in clinical trials with that--
Little skank. Worthless.
This new guy. He's broke?
That's right, ma'am.
Then hit him even harder
so he won't be able
to use his powers at all.
Should I block all his income streams?
That'd be boring.
It's really a battle of type advantages.
He needs paper money, right?
Let's burn it.
Wait a minute.
We still need some clinical trials
for that, don't we?
Hi there.
I wanna ask a favor.
Oh, my head.
Excuse me?
I have a question.
What exactly is this all about?
I need to see it with my own eyes
if you've actually inherited it.
Get started.
I should've cooperated
with the authorities
and allowed myself to be
judged according to the law.
I only had one thought
while they were beating me up.
What the hell was my dad thinking
when he told me to call this place?
Hey, you.
-Hey, hey.
-Hey!
What's with this punk?
-Did he pass out?
-Is he dead?
What the…
-Where is the change coming from?
-What's going on? What is this?
-What's going on?
-What is that?
I realized two things.
One. It did hurt,
but not enough to kill me.
Thanks to the money.
Two.
If I burn through all this cash,
after that, I will actually die.
-Hey!
-Ooh!
What…
-You know, I could just…
-Whoa!
Come on. What are you looking at?
-Huh?
-Whoa!
Huh? I'll get you next. You want some?
Now that there's no money left,
this is hard, and I'm tired.
Come to think of it,
things have been rough.
I've been tired my whole life.
Everyone out.
So you did inherit it.
Is your father doing well?
In Spain.
Traveling.
He swindled me out of my money,
and now he's traveling to Spain?
With that little hussy?
You know, if your father had married me,
he could've purchased
his own Spanish island.
That moron could've had it all.
Anyway, including the cost of the test,
it's three billion, five million won.
You need to pay it.
Compound interest keeps growing,
even right now.
In addition to this damned superpower,
as my second inheritance,
I've been given three billion in debt
to a shady third-party
financial institution.
Sorry, but, uh,
I think it'd be better
if I talked to my dad about--
About what, huh? I've got a daughter.
If you're smart,
you'd consider marrying her.
Huh?
Do that, and your money issues
will all be forgotten.
Dear God.
It's straight out of a daytime soap opera.
If you were my son-in-law,
I promise you'd never be broke again.
My daughter's very pretty like me.
A beauty.
Oh.
That's great. Good for you.
Your girlfriend.
Is she why you're hesitant?
Don't be stupid.
You listen here.
Leave now, and you won't last on your own.
You won't last more than a day
without someone helping you.
Those guys are never gonna
let you get away.
And, um, who are those guys exactly?
Did oppa not tell you all that?
He's just as irresponsible now
as he was back then.
They're waiting.
They're serious psychopaths
you can't handle with the money you make.
So just become my son-in-law
and live with us.
Uh, this can't be real.
Third floor?
I think it's probably around ten meters.
It's 10,000 won for every two meters.
So 50,000.
Hey!
-Why are you pushing me?
-I wasn't pushing. I was supporting you.
Just let him go.
He'll come running back here
when he's out of cash.
Wow.
Ah, damn it.
Ah! Seriously.
-Why? Ah!
-So what happened?
Were you waiting here all night?
This is you, isn't it?
UNBELIEVABLE
BREAKING DOWN THE BUS CRASH
ALIEN?
SUPERHUMAN?
UNBELIEVABLE POWER
EYEWITNESS TESTIMONIES
INSANE POWER, WHO IS HE?
A KOREAN-STYLE SUPERHERO?!
Everyone's seen it. You're famous.
I was…
Hey, listen, I can explain this.
Mm-hmm. So explain it.
What do I tell her?
How much do I tell her?
That I blew all my mom's money
and got arrested,
and then got caught by loan sharks,
which landed me
with three billion in debt.
How much did you use?
And where'd you get it?
If I tell the truth, Min-suk will kill me.
-Where'd you get the money from?
-My mother.
Her savings pool cash.
How much?
-Listen, Min-suk.
-I'll just ask your mom myself.
Wait, wait.
It was 30
million.
I was going home
after she gave me the cash.
All of a sudden,
there was a bus accident right there.
What was I supposed to do?
Huh?
So-jeong is getting married.
At Cheongdam Hotel.
Really?
She wants you there.
She's gonna… throw me the bouquet.
-We should go, then. We can take a--
-It's okay.
I don't know about us.
I'm really good at catching.
-I'll catch it for you, don't worry.
-How could you be so stupid?
You said there was nowhere
to even use your powers!
Min-suk.
Min-suk. Wait. Let me explain.
Please. Just hear me out.
Min-suk, I just…
Min-suk.
Just wait!
Hey, Min-suk!
Wait, please!
Just wait. Could you wait a second?
Hear me out, okay?
Don't do this.
Just let me explain.
Answer the phone.
Come on, Min-suk, answer the phone.
Ah!
Wait. Min-suk.
That's my place.
What the hell?
Oh my God! What are we gonna do?
So when are they coming?
Leave now, you won't last more than a day
without someone helping you.
Tell them to hurry. Quick, quick, quick!
Those guys
are never gonna let you get away.
They're serious psychopaths
you can't handle with the money you make.
Tell them to hurry! Hurry!
Oh my God!
Save it.
What do I do now?
Who were those guys?
Should I just go back to the cops
and turn myself in?
But what crime have I committed?
What if I'm released without charges?
Should I go to the press?
But what if they think I'm crazy?
I'm worried about Min-suk.
I hope she's okay.
MY MIN-SUK (20)
Just pick up, all right? Come on.
The person you're trying
to reach is unavailable. Please--
TO SANG-UNG
You're okay, right?
Min-suk, did something happen to you?
Why aren't you responding?
I know that he'll come for his girlfriend.
I want Kang Sang-ung brought in alive,
even if it means that some people die.
Yes. We'll make it happen.
This one looks like he'll be entertaining.
What was that? What?
What?
Let's go.
This way! Come on! Come on!
FIRE AT CHEONGDAM WEDDING HALL
CHECKING FOR CASUALTIES
We've received reports of a fire.
A short while ago, at around 2:10 p.m.,
a fire broke out
at Cheongdam Hotel in Gangnam, Seoul.
The fire is burning out of control.
So-jeong is getting married.
At Cheongdam Hotel.
She wants you there.
She's gonna throw me the bouquet.
The exact details of the extent of damage…
What?
Wait a minute.
MY MIN-SUK
Come on. Answer, please.
The person
you're trying to reach is unavailable.
Oh, fuck me. What do I do?
I've got no money left.
Oh shit.
Sang-ung.
I saw the news about the bus accident.
TO SANG-UNG
The footage was blurry,
but right away, I knew it was you.
I'm not sure
where you got the money to do it,
but I know the hollow feeling you get
even after you do a good deed.
That's how it was for me too.
It's always that way.
I kept wishing I could do more
for you and your mom,
but something always came up.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Listen, I have an emergency, sir.
Sorry about this. Please cancel it.
I'm sorry.
Unfortunately, you'll have to get
used to that happening.
I would constantly
remind myself that it could be
you or your mother
who was trapped in the overturned car.
Or in the school bus.
Or in the burning building
I was running into.
Honestly, this work is impossible to bear,
unless you think of it that way.
The person you are--
It may be hard, and it may be scary,
but do not run from it.
The person you love
is waiting for you.
Still, I'll give you one piece of advice.
Don't ever…
…touch your savings accounts.
We need to get in there!
Right there.
Somebody help! Help her! Somebody help!
-Somebody help!
-Hurry up!
Hurry!
You know I'm by your side
When everybody turns their back to you
You know where to turn to
I won't ever let you down
Take my hand
Mm-mm
You and I together
Through the fire
Through the thick and thin
We'll get over, you'll be fine
'Cause I'll always be here
And if somebody ever lets you down
I'll run to you to calm you down
I swear, as long as I'm with you
You know you're safe and sound…
I told you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh…
I'm good at catching things.
If somebody ever lets you down
I don't care wherever you are
In the dark
In the fire
I'm the one
I will always be by your side…
I wanna do
All kinds of things with you
Hope you know it's worth it
And if somebody ever lets you down
I'll run to you to calm you down
I swear, as long as I'm with you
You know you're safe and sound
Oh, oh, oh, oh
If somebody ever lets you down
I don't care wherever you are
In the dark
In the fire…
Are you okay?
I'm the one
I will always be by your side…
It's all right.
I'll be that the light for you…
-It's okay.
-I thought I was gonna die.
I'm here. It's okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
Don't you worry cause I'm for you
Where did…
Where did you get the money?
I canceled it.
The subscription savings account.
Are you insane?
Get back! Everybody back!
I think he went out that way.
Oh my God!
You can get out through here.
Heads down. Move slowly.
Through here.
Keep your heads down.
Good. That's it. Watch your head.
Here.
MARRIAGE REGISTRATION FORM
WIFE, KIM MIN-SUK
HUSBAND, KANG SANG-UNG
We'll register a savings account
in your name.
The newlywed bonus.
Apparently, even if we got divorced,
you can still use it.
If you're okay with it…
then we should get married.
I should have known.
Obviously, I wouldn't be
the only person in the world
who could wield a superpower.
Oh God! What is that?
Someone I need some more cash to beat.
What do we do?
Min-suk, get behind me, all right?
Why? Why?
I still got some money here.
Sang-ung, be careful.
Sang-ung!
My money. Damn it.
It burns!
Sang-ung!
Damn it.
Kang Sang-ung!
Wait.
I don't know what you're planning, okay.
Can you just leave him alone?
Hey!
Stay away.
Damn it. Just stay back, all right?
I had to put you out.
You set deadly fires
and tried crushing people.
You bastard! It's too damn hot in here!
What a jerk.
Oh, I'm so glad you're okay.
Are you okay? Huh?
Sang-ung, where'd you get money
to do that?
It's really hot.
Huh?
It wasn't So-jeong's gift money?
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR WEDDING
Uh. Yeah, that's So-jeong's gift money.
Oh great.
Sang-ung!
Sang-ung! Sang-ung!
Kang Sang-ung, stay with me, okay?
You're okay. It's okay.
Sang-ung.
Over there.
So you're Sang-ung.
How's your dad? Is he all right?
Who are these people?
What the hell did my dad
spend all his time doing?
Your dad has bought me
a whole bunch of drinks over the years.
Just breathe slowly, all right?
You're okay.
Bun-mi. That guy.
He's using Hwa-jin's powers, isn't he?
Yeah. Yeah, I think he is.
Hold on. Wait.
Who are…
The Society of Korean Superhumans.
This is bad.
I'm in trouble.
Actually, I'm dead meat.
I'm ready for whatever
I am ready to roll
Every move I make, I'm breaking free
To live this moment
No worries, no more fears
Moving on here and now
Every time, every breath
Taking chances to the fullest
Never looking back
Forget about me, my yesterday
We're turning the page
Taking on the world
Feeling the rush, new day begins
Making the most of every day
Every scar and every tear
They made me who I am
For in this brand-new day
There's just nothing left to hide
Forget about yesterday
No worries, no more fears
Moving on here and now
Every time, every breath
Living life to the fullest
Never looking back
Forget about me, my yesterday
We're turning the page
Taking on the world
Feeling the rush, new day begins
Making the most of every day
Every scar and every tear
They made me who I am
For in this brand-new day
There's just nothing left to hide
Forget about yesterday
Forget about my yesterday
We're turning the page
Taking on the world
Feeling the rush, new day begins
Making the most of every day
Every scar and every tear
They made me who I am
For in this brand-new day
There's just nothing left to hide
Forget about yesterday
Forget about the past
Forget it
Forget about yesterday